# Dor Halevy

B.Sc. Graduate - Neuroscience and Psychology. Responsible for research, development, analysis, and growth as a Data Specialist in my unit. good organizational and management ability, good interpersonal skills, ambition, and self-motivated. experienced with data analysis and programming in various platforms. has the ability to learn fast and the will to use it for learning and extending my knowledge and capabilities.





halevydor@gmail.com



0524536476



Tel-Aviv



in linkedin.com/in/dor-halevy

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **B.sc** - Neuroscience

Ben-Gurion University of the Negev

10/2018 - 08/2021

Relevant Courses

- Experimental Methods
- Multivariate Analysis Methods
- Cognitive and Social Psychology
- Computational Analysis

# **Certified Data Scientist Bar-Ilan University**

10/2021 - Present

Relevant Courses

- Machine Learning specialization
- Statistics

- Predictive Models
- Programing

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Data Specialist**

Planck Data

05/2022 - Present

- Achievements/Tasks Data analysis and Modeling
- Creating new tools and automating processes
- Product Strategy

#### Lecturer

Jolt

10/2021 - Present

Achievements/Tasks

- Professional course management
- Individual and team instruction

#### Marketing Data Analyst Ryze

01/2021 - 05/2022

Achievements/Tasks

- Optimization Analysis
- Large Budgets management

#### **Research Assistant**

Ben-Gurion University of the Negev

01/2020 - 08/2021

Achievements/Tasks

- Data Analysis and Research development
- Laboratory project management

### **SKILLS**



## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

PERACH Scholarship - Graduated with honors (2019)

needy childern tutor at the PERACH's enrichment center.

Setting up an independent business (2017)

OutDor Fitness and massage - therapy and sport

Vootto (2016)

startup - Consulting and development

Graduated with honors in Military Officers Course (2015)

Full graduate with honors certificate, Score- 105 (2012)

10 units-Biotechnology

# **LANGUAGES**

**Enalish** 

Full Professional Proficiency

Hebrew

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

## **INTERESTS**

